

8	Thane, Maharashtra
	+91 83698 91137



## WHO AM I?

Successful **Software Engineer** with 5 years of professional experience. Seeking a challenging career with a reputable organization to fully utilize my experience and skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.



## **EXPERIENCE**

10/2018 - 12/2021 Whitefield Bangalore Systems Engineer

Tata Consultancy Services

Whitefield, Bangalore Designed two new logical system environments by implementing new Data

Distribution Model and Partner Profiles

Fixed recurring issues such as data inconsistencies between two systems by providing

RCA and resolution

Successfully leading a team of size 4 since December 2020

Core Java / SAP ABAP / SQL

12/2021 - Present Andheri, Mumbai **Systems Engineer** 

**NSEIT Limited** 

Designed two new logical system environments by implementing new Data

Distribution Model and Partner Profiles

Fixed recurring issues such as data inconsistencies between two systems by providing

RCA and resolution

Successfully leading a team of size 4 since December 2020

Core Java / Golang / Postgresql

## **EDUCATION**

6/2014 - 6/2018
Wadala, Mumbai

3/2012 - 3/2014
Ghatkopar, Mumbai

Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology
Vidyalankar Institute of Technology, University of Mumbai

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Science
Ramniranjan Jhujhunwala College, Maharashtra Board

Secondary School Certificate, Maharashtra Board
Pune Vidyarthi Griha's Vidya Bhawan

CGPA - 8.125 / 10

Percentage - 84.75 / 100

Percentage - 92.18 / 100

LANGUAGES

English - Proficient Hindi - Proficient Marathi - Native HOBBIES

Table tennis